Introduction
Chapter 1 Facing Reality and Accepting the Truth
Chapter 2 Learning from Mistakes and Turning Pain into Progress
Chapter 3 Building a System of Principles for Consistent Decision-Making
Chapter 4 Creating a Culture of Radical Honesty and Transparency
Chapter 5 Embracing Thoughtful Disagreement and the Power of Idea Meritocracy
Chapter 6 Systematizing Decision-Making: The Power of Algorithms and Checklists
Chapter 7 Building Effective Teams: Aligning Values, Abilities, and Roles
Chapter 8 Diagnosing Problems and Designing Solutions
Chapter 9 Implementing and Iterating: The Discipline of Execution
Chapter 10 Sustaining Success: Continuous Learning and Adaptation
Conclusion